buyatimeshare.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Buy Sell and Rent Timeshares

**Your access to and use of this website is governed by the[TERM Of USE](http://www.buyatimeshare.com/terms.asp) and the following PRIVACY NOTICE.  Please read them carefully as they constitute a legally binding agreement applicable to all users of this website.  If you do not agree with these terms, you should refrain from using this website.**

 **Last Updated:   February 20, 2014**

Welcome to our website, which is operated by VP Resales, LLC (referred to as “Operator, “we,” “us” or “our”).  VP Resales, LLC and its affiliates also operate several other websites, including www.Buyatimeshare.com, www.Sellatimeshare.com, www.VPResales.com, www.VacationPropertyResales.com and www.Rent-Timeshare-today.com (which, with this website, are referred to collectively as the “Website”)

This Privacy Notice explains how we protect your privacy, what information we collect from you and the other people who visit the Website (collectively, the "Users"), and how we use that information.  This Privacy Notice is specifically incorporated into our [Terms of Use,](http://www.buyatimeshare.com/terms.asp) which governs the use of the Website generally.    

Please read the Privacy Notice and our  [Terms of Use](http://www.buyatimeshare.com/terms.asp) carefully before providing any information.  By accessing the Website or providing any information, you agree to our use of that information consistent with the Privacy Notice.  If you have questions about this Privacy Notice, email us at [info@buyatimeshare.com](mailto:info@buyatimeshare.com).  To assist us in processing your request, please include the phrase “Question – Privacy Notice” in the header of the email.

 **PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We collect personally identifiable information from our Users at several different points on our Website. When this Privacy Notice uses the term "personally identifiable information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as the individual's name, postal address, email address, payment information, telephone number, IP address, etc. When other information, such as consumer preferences, is directly associated with personally identifiable information, this other information also becomes personally identifiable information for purposes of this Privacy Notice.

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. However, no internet platform or database is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure, interception or misuse. Therefore, you are advised to take precautions when transmitting personally identifiable information (i.e., communicating with a potential purchaser for your timeshare). As there is no way for us to ensure or guarantee the privacy of User information before it arrives at the Website or after it leaves the Website, and we are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

 **INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

 **Information That You Provide**

We collect and store information you enter on the Website.  All Users have the option of providing various types of personally identifiable information to us through the Website.  To perform the services offered through the Website, we need to collect and distribute personally identifiable information.  We are committed to the responsible handling of any personal information you provide to us.  This means we will use it only as outlined below.  Users are welcome to browse our Website.  However, to participate in some of our services, Users will be required to complete brief registration forms or enter other information.  These forms may ask for personally identifiable information, including your name, address, phone numbers, and credit card information.  When personally identifiable information is collected, it is subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice.  Information entered by Users may be transmitted to our trusted business partners who fulfill the services requested by those Users.  We may also use information entered by you to respond to your requests and communicate with you.

We encourage you to provide your personally identifiable information to us so you to take full advantage of the Website.  Providing your personally identifiable information, however, is completely voluntary.  You may choose not to provide us with your personally identifiable information.  You will still have access to the Website even if you do not provide us with your personally identifiable information, but you will not be able to use certain services or features available through the Website that require you to enter your personally identifiable information to function.

 **Information Collected Automatically**

We receive and store certain types of information each time you access the Website. We log your IP address to help us to diagnose problems with our servers, administer the Website, and track usage statistics. We match IP addresses to completed User registration forms for validation and error checking purposes. If you reached the Website by clicking on a link or ad from another website, then we may also log that information. This helps us to maximize our Internet exposure and to understand the interests of our Users. In general, this information is used to generate overall anonymous reports on our Users that enable us to improve the effectiveness of the Website.

We also engage in online behavioral advertising, also known as interest-based advertising, so that third-party advertising companies can display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online. These third-party companies may over time collect certain information about you when you visit this Website and other websites and use that information to serve ads for our services or for the products or services of other companies likely to be of interest to you. These parties typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information.

 **Data Tracking**

CookiesWhen you visit the Website, we may send one or more small files known as "cookies" to your computer.  A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through the Website and to determine whether you have visited us before.  However, unless you provide us with personally identifiable information, the cookies will not contain any information that would allow us to personally identify you.  If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, the cookie is tied to this information so that our systems will recognize you each time you visit the Website.  In that way, we can save your preferences from visit to visit and present you with a customized version of the Website, without requiring you to log into the Website every time you visit. Our cookies cannot be used to read any other data from your computer and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other Websites.  We use cookies to help us understand how Users use the Website, and to help us to improve the Website.  You may refuse to accept a cookie from us by following the procedures for rejecting cookies specific to your web browser.   Although you may do so, you may find that your browser reacts strangely when visiting not only our Website, but other websites as well. 

If you visit the website of one of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) by clicking on a link from our Website, they may also use cookies on their website.  We have no access to or control over these cookies.  This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by us only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or other websites.

 **User Activity Tracking**

We may employ software technology that enables us to track certain aspects of a User's visit to the Website.  This technology helps us better manage content on the Website by informing us what content is effective.  The software typically uses two methods to track User activity: 1) "trackers" and 2) "clear gifs".  Trackers are pieces of executable code that are embedded in a web page that track usage activity including which pages are viewed, when they are viewed, and how long the pages are viewed.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers, which are embedded in web pages and email messages that track whether or not a User has viewed a particular web page or email message.  User activity information may be associated with additional information about a User's session, such as IP Address and the type of browser used, and personally identifiable information, if provided by the User.

If you arrive at the Website by "clicking through" from another website, and you have registered with that other website, then certain information about you that you provided to that other website, such as the terms you were searching on that led you to the Website, may be transmitted to us and we may use it.  You should review the Privacy Notice of any website from which you reached the Website in order to determine what information was collected by that website and for what purpose(s) you agreed that website could use that information.   We may or may not retain information about you provided to us by other websites.  If we do, we will only use it in accordance with this Privacy Notice.  Such information may or may not be associated with other User activity data or personally identifiable information.

 **Use of "Do Not Track" Software**

At this time, our systems do not respond to browser "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that allow you to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information over time or across third-party websites or online services.

 **Social Media Widgets**

The Website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google Plus, Pinterest, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you're visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

 **HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

 **General Uses of Information**

We may use the information (whether or not personally identifiable) that you provide to us to:

  * Make your next visit to the Website more personalized; 
  * Process or complete transactions requested by you; 
  * Contact you regarding administrative issues, such as questions about your specific request; 
  * Email information and offers to you; 
  * Mail information and offers to you; 
  * Make telephone calls to you with information and offers; 
  * Provide your information to trusted business partners to fulfill services you have requested; 
  * Compile anonymous statistical information and analyses; 
  * Provide compiled anonymous information to third parties; and 
  * Provide, sell, or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties for advertising purposes. 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our Website may request personally identifiable information from Users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the User therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Website. Users' personally identifiable information collected through surveys or contests may be shared with our trusted business partners and other third parties as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

 **About the Process You are Using**

We offer to advertise timeshares owned by one person to those interested in buying or renting those timeshares.  If you choose to offer to sell, buy or rent a timeshare, any information collected from you by the party receiving the offer will not be governed by this Privacy Notice.   We are not responsible for the policies or practices of those receiving any information about you as a result of your correspondence regarding the sale, purchase or rental of a timeshare.  We expressly disclaim any and all liability or responsibility whatsoever for the success or suitability of any such business dealing.  Final assessment of any offer or timeshare sold, purchased or rented, including the fairness and accuracy of such transaction, and the task of seeing any transaction through to its conclusion is solely the User’s responsibility.  We do not function as a buyer or seller agent in any way and do not represent any party in any transaction.  

 **Consent to the Use of Third Party Providers**

We may contract with third parties to provide various services relating to the Website on an outsourced basis. For example, we may contract with an email provider to handle the distribution of email messages to Users of the Website; with a website hosting provider to host the Website for us; and with various validation services to confirm contact information that you provide. We may also share information provided by Users (whether or not personally identifiable) with certain trusted business partners, who in turn will use that information to market products or services likely to be of interest to you, or provide you with special offers and opportunities.

By visiting the Website, all Users consent to us providing all information (whether or not personally identifiable) received or collected from those Users to such third parties for the purposes described above. In addition, all Users consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of such information (whether or not personally identifiable) by us and these third parties. To opt out of our sharing of your personal information, see "Opting Out" below.

 **Other Websites**

Please be aware that our affiliated institutions, promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party websites accessible through the Website may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.  We are not responsible for any actions, content of websites or privacy policies of such third parties.  You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information through linked websites.

 **Protection of Operator and Others**

We may release account information and other personally identifiable information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with applicable law, to enforce our legal and contractual rights, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Operator, Users, or others.  We may in some circumstances be required to disclose information (including personally identifiable information) in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process.  We may also turn over information about you if we believe we must do so in order to prevent a violation of the law, and by accepting this Privacy Notice, you consent to our right to do so, in our sole discretion.  You also consent to our disclosing information about you in the course of legal proceedings if we believe we are legally required to do so, if we reasonably believe that doing so may mitigate our liability, or if doing so will assist us.  

 **Business Transfers**

At some point, we may establish subsidiaries or other related companies, or merge with or be acquired by another company.  When that happens, then we may disclose to them your personally identifiable information, in which case we will request them to abide by this Privacy Notice.  We may also disclose some personally identifiable information to a potential acquirer, although such disclosure would be subject to normal and customary confidentiality requirements.

 **CHILDREN**

The Website is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

 **OPTING OUT**

If you do not agree to the use of your personally identifiable information as described above, you are not required to provide that information to us. If you have provided information and would prefer not to have your information shared, you may opt out by emailing [info@buyatimeshare.com](mailto:info@buyatimeshare.com) or calling us at (800) 882-0296. To assist us in processing your email request, please include the phrase "Opt Out" in the header of the email. Please note that we may need to share your information with certain third parties in order to provide the services you have requested. However, if you opt out, we will not share your information with any third parties for marketing purposes.

 **COMMUNICATIONS FROM US**

We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will contact you either through email, telephone, or postal mail.

When it is necessary to do so, we will send you service-related announcements, primarily via email. For example, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send you email. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by e-mailing [info@buyatimeshare.com](mailto:info@buyatimeshare.com).  To assist us in processing your request, please include the phrase “Deactivate Account” in the header of the email.

 **UPDATING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION**

You may correct and update your personally identifiable information by logging into your account or sending us an email at [info@buyatimeshare.com](mailto:info@buyatimeshare.com).  To assist us in processing your request, please include the phrase “Update Information” in the header of the email.  You may also send us a letter with your specific request at the following address:

 **BuyATimeshare Attention: Information Update 32 Daniel Webster Hwy #25 Merrimack, NH 03054**

Please provide your name, address, email address, and the information that you would like us to update.  You may ask to have to have information deleted or removed.  However, you cannot delete information included with past transactions, and it may not be possible for us to completely delete all of your information from backup media. 

 **PRIVACY NOTICE CHANGES**

If we materially change this Privacy Notice, we will post the changes to this Privacy Notice and notify you of the change as we deem appropriate.  We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Notice at any time, so please review the Website frequently for any changes.  Amendments to this Privacy Notice will be posted on the Website and will be effective when posted.  You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted, the changes to any amended or revised Privacy Notice by your continued use of our services or the Website.

 **CONTACT US**

If you have questions specifically about this Privacy Notice, or to legal issues pertaining to the practices of the Website or your use of the Website, you may contact us via email at [info@buyatimeshare.com](mailto:info@buyatimeshare.com).  You may also send us a letter at the following address:

**BuyATimeshare 32 Daniel Webster Hwy #25 Merrimack, NH 03054**
